Guide to the Cornell University News Service records, [ca. 1920s-2000s].
Cornell University News Service records
- Series VI. Cornell University News Services records, 1920s-2000s
  - Press Releases, News Clippings, Distribution Lists, Administrative Files, Subject Files
    - General
      - Vegetable Crops, 1973 (Box 4-3-15 - 46, Folder 24)
      - Vegetable Crops, 1974-1975 (Box 4-3-15 - 46, Folder 25)
      - Vegetable Crops, 1976-1979 (Box 4-3-15 - 46, Folder 26)
      - Veterinary College, 1950s (Box 4-3-15 - 46, Folder 27)
      - Veterinary College, 1960s (Box 4-3-15 - 46, Folder 28)
      - Veterinary College, 1970s (Box 4-3-15 - 46, Folder 29)
      - Arecibo Clippings, 1970s (Box 4-3-15 - 47, Folder 1)
      - Arecibo Background Information, 1970s (Box 4-3-15 - 47, Folder 2)
      - Pulsar's, 1960s (Box 4-3-15 - 47, Folder 3)
      - Armory (Box 4-3-15 - 47, Folder 4)
      - Attrition Rate (Box 4-3-15 - 47, Folder 5)
      - Baird, Thomas - Visiting Critic Fund (Box 4-3-15 - 47, Folder 6)
      - Baker Lab (Box 4-3-15 - 47, Folder 7)
      - Bakke Case: Clippings and Releases (Box 4-3-15 - 47, Folder 8)
      - Bakke Case: Background Information (Box 4-3-15 - 47, Folder 9)
      - Banking (Box 4-3-15 - 47, Folder 10)
      - Barron's (Box 4-3-15 - 47, Folder 11)
      - Bausch Metallographic Lab (Box 4-3-15 - 47, Folder 12)
      - Bethe Report (Box 4-3-15 - 47, Folder 13)
      - Bethlehem Steel Program (Box 4-3-15 - 47, Folder 14)
      - Press Releases, 1979 (Box 4-3-15 - 47, Folder 15)
      - Press Releases, 1979 (Box 4-3-15 - 47, Folder 16)
      - Press Releases, 1979 (Box 4-3-15 - 47, Folder 17)
      - Press Releases, 1977 (Box 4-3-15 - 47, Folder 18)
      - Press Releases, October 1977 (Box 4-3-15 - 47, Folder 19)
      - Press Releases, 1977 (Box 4-3-15 - 47, Folder 20)
      - Press Releases, 1979-1980 (Box 4-3-15 - 47, Folder 21)
      - Press Releases, 1980-1982 (Box 4-3-15 - 47, Folder 22)
      - Misc. Papers, 1980s (Box 4-3-15 - 47, Folder 23)
      - Forefronts, 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 47, Folder 24)
      - Center for Theory, 1985-1989 (Box 4-3-15 - 47, Folder 25)
      - Cornell in the News, 1987-1990 (Box 4-3-15 - 47, Folder 26)
      - Cornell in the News, 1990-1991 (Box 4-3-15 - 47, Folder 27)
      - Fiske Islandic Collection (Box 4-3-15 - 47, Folder 28)
      - Shakespeare Collection, 1954 (Box 4-3-15 - 47, Folder 29)
      - Petrarch Collection (Box 4-3-15 - 47, Folder 30)
      - Lewis Collection (Box 4-3-15 - 47, Folder 31)
      - History of Science Collection (Box 4-3-15 - 47, Folder 32)
      - Franco-American Collection (Box 4-3-15 - 47, Folder 33)
      - Cornelliana Collection (Box 4-3-15 - 47, Folder 34)
      - Wason Collection (Box 4-3-15 - 47, Folder 35)
      - Witchcraft Collection (Box 4-3-15 - 47, Folder 36)
      - Wordsworth Collection (Box 4-3-15 - 47, Folder 37)
      - The Joyce Collection (Box 4-3-15 - 47, Folder 38)
      - William R. George Republic Papers, 1895-1970 (Box 4-3-15 - 47, Folder 39)
      - Noyes Collection of Historical Americana (Box 4-3-15 - 47, Folder 40)
      - Lafayette Collection (Box 4-3-15 - 47, Folder 41)
      - Library Collection (Box 4-3-15 - 47, Folder 42)
      - Press Summary, 1967-1969 (Box 4-3-15 - 48, Folder 1)
      - Press Summary, 1970-1973 (Box 4-3-15 - 48, Folder 2)
      - Press Summary, 1974-1977 (Box 4-3-15 - 48, Folder 3)
      - Press Releases, 1977 (Box 4-3-15 - 48, Folder 4)
      - Press Releases, May 1977 (Box 4-3-15 - 48, Folder 5)
      - Press Releases, June-July 1977 (Box 4-3-15 - 48, Folder 6)
      - Press Releases, August 1977 (Box 4-3-15 - 48, Folder 7)
      - News Releases (Bound Book - v. 1), 1977/1978 (Box 4-3-15 - 48)
      - News Releases (Bound Book - v. 2), 1977/1978 (Box 4-3-15 - 48)
      - Press Summary, 1978-1980 (Box 4-3-15 - 48, Folder 8)
      - Press Releases, Winter 1977-1978 (Box 4-3-15 - 48, Folder 9)
      - Press Releases, February 1978 (Box 4-3-15 - 48, Folder 10)
      - Press Releases, March 1978 (Box 4-3-15 - 48, Folder 11)
      - Press Releases, April 1978 (Box 4-3-15 - 48, Folder 12)
      - Press Releases, May 1978 (Box 4-3-15 - 48, Folder 13)
      - Press Releases, Summer 1978 (Box 4-3-15 - 48, Folder 14)
      - Press Releases, September 1978 (Box 4-3-15 - 48, Folder 15)
      - Press Releases, October 1978 (Box 4-3-15 - 48, Folder 16)
      - Press Releases, November-December 1978 (Box 4-3-15 - 48, Folder 17)
      - Press Summary, 1979-1983 (Box 4-3-15 - 48, Folder 18)
      - News Releases (Bound Book v. 1), 1978/1979 (Box 4-3-15 - 49)
      - News Releases (Bound Book v. 2), 1978/1979 (Box 4-3-15 - 49)
      - Press Releases, January 1979 (Box 4-3-15 - 49, Folder 1)
      - Press Releases, May 1980 (Box 4-3-15 - 49, Folder 2)
      - Press Releases, Summer 1980 (Box 4-3-15 - 49, Folder 3)
      - Press Releases, Summer 1980 (Box 4-3-15 - 49, Folder 4)
      - State College (CALS and Human Ecology) Press Releases, March 1980 (Box 4-3-15 - 49, Folder 5)
      - State College Press Releases, May 1980 (Box 4-3-15 - 49, Folder 6)
      - State College Press Releases, July 1980 (Box 4-3-15 - 49, Folder 7)
      - Press Releases, September 1980 (Box 4-3-15 - 49, Folder 8)
      - Press Releases, October 1980 (Box 4-3-15 - 49, Folder 9)
      - Press Releases, October 1980 (Box 4-3-15 - 49, Folder 10)
      - State College Press Releases, November 1980 (Box 4-3-15 - 49, Folder 11)
      - Press Releases, November-December 1980 (Box 4-3-15 - 49, Folder 12)
      - Press Summary, 1981-1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 49, Folder 13)
      - Press Releases, January 1981 (Box 4-3-15 - 49, Folder 14)
      - State College Press Releases, January 1981 (Box 4-3-15 - 49, Folder 15)
      - Press Releases, March 1981 (Box 4-3-15 - 49, Folder 16)
      - Press Releases, April 1981 (Box 4-3-15 - 49, Folder 17)
      - Press Releases, May 1981 (Box 4-3-15 - 49, Folder 18)
      - Press Releases, February 1981 (Box 4-3-15 - 49, Folder 19)
      - State College Press Releases, March-April 1981 (Box 4-3-15 - 50, Folder 1)
      - State College Press Releases, May-June 1981 (Box 4-3-15 - 50, Folder 2)
      - State College Press Releases, July 1981 (Box 4-3-15 - 50, Folder 3)
      - Press Releases, August-September 1981 (Box 4-3-15 - 50, Folder 4)
      - State College Press Releases, September 1981 (Box 4-3-15 - 50, Folder 5)
      - Press Releases, October 1981 (Box 4-3-15 - 50, Folder 6)
      - State College Press Releases, November 1981 (Box 4-3-15 - 50, Folder 7)
      - Press Releases, November-December 1981 (Box 4-3-15 - 50, Folder 8)
      - State College Press Releases, January 1982 (Box 4-3-15 - 50, Folder 9)
      - Press Releases, January-February 1982 (Box 4-3-15 - 50, Folder 10)
      - Press Releases, March 1982 (Box 4-3-15 - 50, Folder 11)
      - State College Press Releases, March-April 1982 (Box 4-3-15 - 50, Folder 12)
      - Press Releases, April 1982 (Box 4-3-15 - 50, Folder 13)
      - Press Releases, May 1982 (Box 4-3-15 - 50, Folder 14)
      - Press Releases, June-July 1982 (Box 4-3-15 - 50, Folder 15)
      - State College Press Releases, May-June 1982 (Box 4-3-15 - 50, Folder 16)
      - State College Press Releases, July-August 1982 (Box 4-3-15 - 50, Folder 17)
      - Press Releases, August-September 1982 (Box 4-3-15 - 50, Folder 18)
      - State College Press Releases, September-October 1982 (Box 4-3-15 - 50, Folder 19)
      - Press Releases, October 1982 (Box 4-3-15 - 50, Folder 20)
      - State College Press Releases, November-December 1982 (Box 4-3-15 - 50, Folder 21)
      - Press Releases, November-December 1982 (Box 4-3-15 - 50, Folder 22)
      - State College Press Releases, January-February 1983 (Box 4-3-15 - 51, Folder 1)
      - Press Releases, January-February 1983 (Box 4-3-15 - 51, Folder 2)
      - State College Press Releases, March-April 1983 (Box 4-3-15 - 51, Folder 3)
      - Press Releases, March-April 1983 (Box 4-3-15 - 51, Folder 4)
      - Press Releases, May 1983 (Box 4-3-15 - 51, Folder 5)
      - State College Press Releases, June 1983 (Box 4-3-15 - 51, Folder 6)
      - Press Releases, June-July 1983 (Box 4-3-15 - 51, Folder 7)
      - Press Releases (And State College Press Releases), July-August 1983 (Box 4-3-15 - 51, Folder 8)
      - Press Releases, September 1983 (Box 4-3-15 - 51, Folder 9)
      - Press Releases, September-October 1983 (Box 4-3-15 - 51, Folder 10)
      - State College Press Releases, September-October 1983 (Box 4-3-15 - 51, Folder 11)
      - Press Releases, November-December 1983 (Box 4-3-15 - 51, Folder 12)
      - State College Press Releases, November-December 1983 (Box 4-3-15 - 51, Folder 13)
      - State College Press Releases, January-March 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 51, Folder 14)
      - Press Releases, January-February 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 51, Folder 15)
      - Press Releases, March-April 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 51, Folder 16)
      - State College Press Releases, April-June 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 51, Folder 17)
      - Press Releases, May-June 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 51, Folder 18)
      - State College Press Releases, July-September 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 51, Folder 19)
      - Press Releases, July-August 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 51, Folder 20)
      - Press Releases, September 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 51, Folder 21)
      - Press Releases (And State College Releases), October 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 51, Folder 22)
      - Press Releases (And State College Releases), November 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 51, Folder 23)
      - Press Releases, December 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 51, Folder 24)
      - Cornell Related Clippings, May-June 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 52, Folder 1)
      - Press Releases, January-February 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 52, Folder 2)
      - Press Releases, March-April 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 52, Folder 3)
      - Press Releases, May-June 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 52, Folder 4)
      - Press Releases, July-August 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 52, Folder 5)
      - Press Releases, September-October 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 52, Folder 6)
      - Press Releases, November-December 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 52, Folder 7)
      - Press Releases, January-February 1986 (Box 4-3-15 - 52, Folder 8)
      - Press Releases, March-April 1986 (Box 4-3-15 - 52, Folder 9)
      - Press Releases, May-June 1986 (Box 4-3-15 - 52, Folder 10)
      - Press Releases, July-August 1986 (Box 4-3-15 - 52, Folder 11)
      - Press Releases, September-October 1986 (Box 4-3-15 - 52, Folder 12)
      - Press Releases, March-April 1987 (Box 4-3-15 - 52, Folder 13)
      - Press Releases, May 1987 (Box 4-3-15 - 52, Folder 14)
      - Press Releases, September-October 1987 (Box 4-3-15 - 52, Folder 15)
      - Press Releases, November-December 1987 (Box 4-3-15 - 52, Folder 16)
      - Press Releases, January 1988 (Box 4-3-15 - 52, Folder 17)
      - Memoranda, October 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 53, Folder 1)
      - Releases with Distribution Lists, October 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 53, Folder 2)
      - Releases with Distribution Lists, October 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 53, Folder 3)
      - Releases with Distribution Lists, October 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 53, Folder 4)
      - Releases with Distribution Lists, October 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 53, Folder 5)
      - Releases with Distribution Lists, November 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 53, Folder 6)
      - Releases with Distribution Lists, November 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 53, Folder 7)
      - Releases with Distribution Lists, November 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 53, Folder 8)
      - Blank Stationary (Box 4-3-15 - 53, Folder 9)
      - Memoranda, November 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 53, Folder 10)
      - Bulletin Board, 1986 (Box 4-3-15 - 53, Folder 11)
      - Releases with Distribution Lists, November 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 53, Folder 12)
      - Releases with Distribution Lists, November 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 53, Folder 13)
      - Releases with Distribution Lists, November 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 53, Folder 14)
      - Releases with Distribution Lists, October 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 53, Folder 15)
      - Releases with Distribution Lists, October 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 53, Folder 16)
      - Releases with Distribution Lists, October 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 53, Folder 17)
      - Releases with Distribution Lists, October 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 53, Folder 18)
      - Memoranda, December 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 53, Folder 19)
      - Releases with Distribution Lists, December 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 53, Folder 20)
      - Releases with Distribution Lists, December 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 53, Folder 21)
      - Releases with Distribution Lists, December 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 53, Folder 22)
      - Releases with Distribution Lists, December 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 53, Folder 23)
      - Releases with Distribution Lists, December 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 53, Folder 24)
      - Memoranda, December 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 53, Folder 25)
      - Press Releases, December 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 53, Folder 26)
      - Releases with Distribution Lists, December 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 53, Folder 27)
      - Releases with Distribution Lists, December 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 53, Folder 28)
      - Releases with Distribution Lists, March 1986 (Box 4-3-15 - 53, Folder 29)
      - Memoranda, January 1986 (Box 4-3-15 - 53, Folder 30)
      - Press Releases, January 1986 (Box 4-3-15 - 53, Folder 31)
      - Releases with Distribution Lists, January 1985, 1986 (Box 4-3-15 - 53, Folder 32)
      - Releases with Distribution Lists, January 1986 (Box 4-3-15 - 53, Folder 33)
      - Releases with Distribution Lists, January 1986 (Box 4-3-15 - 53, Folder 34)
      - Memoranda (Box 4-3-15 - 53, Folder 35)
      - Chronicle Only, February 1986 (Box 4-3-15 - 53, Folder 36)
      - Press Releases, February 1986 (Box 4-3-15 - 53, Folder 37)
      - Releases with Distribution Lists, February 1986 (Box 4-3-15 - 53, Folder 38)
      - Releases with Distribution Lists, March 1986 (Box 4-3-15 - 53, Folder 39)
      - Northeast Farm Communicators Newsletters, 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 54, Folder 1)
      - News Summaries, 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 54, Folder 2)
      - CALS and Human Ecology Press Releases, January 1-15, 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 54, Folder 3)
      - CALS and Human Ecology Press Releases, January 16-31, 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 54, Folder 4)
      - CALS and Human Ecology Press Releases, February 1-15, 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 54, Folder 5)
      - CALS and Human Ecology Press Releases, February 16-28, 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 54, Folder 6)
      - CALS and Human Ecology Press Releases, March 1-15, 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 54, Folder 7)
      - CALS and Human Ecology Press Releases, March 16-31, 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 54, Folder 8)
      - CALS and Human Ecology Press Releases, April 1-15, 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 54, Folder 9)
      - CALS and Human Ecology Press Releases, April 16-30, 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 54, Folder 10)
      - CALS and Human Ecology Press Releases, May 1-15, 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 54, Folder 11)
      - CALS and Human Ecology Press Releases, May 16-31, 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 54, Folder 12)
      - CALS and Human Ecology Press Releases, June 1-15, 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 54, Folder 13)
      - CALS and Human Ecology Press Releases, June 16-30, 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 54, Folder 14)
      - CALS and Human Ecology Press Releases, July 1-15, 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 54, Folder 15)
      - CALS and Human Ecology Press Releases, July 16-31, 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 54, Folder 16)
      - CALS and Human Ecology Press Releases, August 1-15, 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 54, Folder 17)
      - CALS and Human Ecology Press Releases, August 16-31, 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 54, Folder 18)
      - CALS and Human Ecology Press Releases, September 1-15, 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 54, Folder 19)
      - CALS and Human Ecology Press Releases, September 16-30, 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 54, Folder 20)
      - CALS and Human Ecology Press Releases, October 1-15, 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 54, Folder 21)
      - CALS and Human Ecology Press Releases, October 16-31, 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 54, Folder 22)
      - CALS and Human Ecology Press Releases, November 1-15, 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 54, Folder 23)
      - CALS and Human Ecology Press Releases, November 16-30, 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 54, Folder 24)
      - CALS and Human Ecology Press Releases, December 1-15, 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 54, Folder 25)
      - CALS and Human Ecology Press Releases, December 16-31, 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 54, Folder 26)
      - Memoranda, January 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 55, Folder 1)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, January 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 55, Folder 2)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, January 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 55, Folder 3)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, January 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 55, Folder 4)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, January 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 55, Folder 5)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, January 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 55, Folder 6)
      - Memoranda, February 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 55, Folder 7)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, February 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 55, Folder 8)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, February 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 55, Folder 9)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, February 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 55, Folder 10)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, February 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 55, Folder 11)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, February 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 55, Folder 12)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, February 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 55, Folder 13)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, February 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 55, Folder 14)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, February 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 55, Folder 15)
      - Memoranda, March 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 55, Folder 16)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, March 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 55, Folder 17)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, March 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 55, Folder 18)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, March 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 55, Folder 19)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, March 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 55, Folder 20)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, March 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 55, Folder 21)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, March 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 55, Folder 22)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, March 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 55, Folder 23)
      - Invoice Sheet, March 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 55, Folder 24)
      - Memoranda, April 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 55, Folder 25)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, April 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 55, Folder 26)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, April 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 55, Folder 27)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, April 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 55, Folder 28)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, April 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 56, Folder 1a)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, April 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 56, Folder 1b)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, April 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 56, Folder 2)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, April 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 56, Folder 3)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, April 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 56, Folder 4)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, April 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 56, Folder 5)
      - Memoranda, May 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 56, Folder 6)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, May 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 56, Folder 7)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, May 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 56, Folder 8)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, May 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 56, Folder 9)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, May 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 56, Folder 10)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, May 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 56, Folder 11)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, May 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 56, Folder 12)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, May 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 56, Folder 13)
      - Memoranda, June 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 56, Folder 14)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, June 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 56, Folder 15)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, June 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 56, Folder 16)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, June 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 56, Folder 17)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, June 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 56, Folder 18)
      - Memoranda, July 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 56, Folder 19)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, July 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 56, Folder 20)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, July 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 56, Folder 21)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, July 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 56, Folder 22)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, July 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 56, Folder 23)
      - Memoranda, August 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 56, Folder 24)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, August 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 56, Folder 25)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, August 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 56, Folder 26)
      - Memoranda, September 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 57, Folder 1)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, September 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 57, Folder 2)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, September 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 57, Folder 3)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, September 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 57, Folder 4)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, September 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 57, Folder 5)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, September 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 57, Folder 6)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, September 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 57, Folder 7)
      - Press Releases, October 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 57, Folder 8)
      - Memoranda, October 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 57, Folder 9)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, October 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 57, Folder 11)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, October 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 57, Folder 11)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, October 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 57, Folder 12)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, October 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 57, Folder 13)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, October 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 57, Folder 14)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, October 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 57, Folder 15)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, October 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 57, Folder 16)
      - Press Releases, November 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 57, Folder 17)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, November 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 57, Folder 18)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, November 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 57, Folder 19)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, November 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 57, Folder 20)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, November 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 57, Folder 21)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, November 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 57, Folder 22)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, November 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 57, Folder 23)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, November 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 57, Folder 24)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, December 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 57, Folder 25)
      - Press Releases and Distribution Lists, December 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 57, Folder 26)
      - CALS and Human Ecology Press Releases, January 1-15, 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 58, Folder 1)
      - CALS and Human Ecology Press Releases, January 16-31, 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 58, Folder 2)
      - CALS and Human Ecology Press Releases, February 1-15, 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 58, Folder 3)
      - CALS and Human Ecology Press Releases, February 15-28, 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 58, Folder 4)
      - CALS and Human Ecology Press Releases, March 1-15, 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 58, Folder 5)
      - CALS and Human Ecology Press Releases, March 16-31, 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 58, Folder 6)
      - CALS and Human Ecology Press Releases, April 1-15, 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 58, Folder 7)
      - CALS and Human Ecology Press Releases, April 16-30, 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 58, Folder 8)
      - CALS and Human Ecology Press Releases, May 1-15, 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 58, Folder 9)
      - CALS and Human Ecology Press Releases, May 16-31, 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 58, Folder 10)
      - CALS and Human Ecology Press Releases, June 1-15, 1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 58, Folder 11)